<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-01-19T17:02:02-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Scribbling Hope</title><subtitle>Sometimes we don’t get to choose. Sometimes God grabs our hands and leads us on a journey. One we may not understand. One we would not have chosen. But one that shapes, changes, and saves our lives. Because He is merciful. Because He loves us.</subtitle><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><entry><title type="html">Those Moments</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/poetry/faith/2019/01/18/Those-Moments.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Those Moments" /><published>2019-01-18T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-18T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/poetry/faith/2019/01/18/Those-Moments</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/poetry/faith/2019/01/18/Those-Moments.html">&lt;p&gt;Thank You, Abba, for the moments when I get it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those moments when both the aches&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and the joys&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;of life fall away&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and I’m left in Your arms&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;tasting just the tiniest taste of Heaven&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;of Reality&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;of Life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank You, Abba, for the moments&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when I remember why I was created&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;why I was gifted&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;why I was prepared and equipped&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and enabled&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to walk in this weary world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank You, Abba, for the moments when I dance&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in my mind,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in my heart,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in my body.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the responsibilities are lifted,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when the worries are banished,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the wants fade away&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and You are more real&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;than I have ever been.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are Good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are Glorious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are God.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the moment fades…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I remember that I am me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stuck in the ruts of my little life&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;trudging forward one step at a time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I remember where I’m going now&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and there’s a Joy in the journey.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">Thank You, Abba, for the moments when I get it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Breathe</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/faith/2019/01/17/Breathe.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Breathe" /><published>2019-01-17T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-17T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/faith/2019/01/17/Breathe</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/faith/2019/01/17/Breathe.html">&lt;p&gt;I have a friend whose husband is having surgery tomorrow. This one is for him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breathe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;God’s got this. 
God’s got you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ever since before the first breath you took, God’s been there, watching you. 
Loving you. 
Waiting for you to realize Who He is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And He’s still there now. 
Trust Him. 
Take a chance on loving Him back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t promise that when you trust God, everything is perfect. 
I can’t promise that bad things will never happen. 
I can’t promise that life will be all sunshine and walks with the dog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because you already know that’s not true. 
You’ve already held more pain in your heart than any human should. 
And sadly, I’m sure there’s more pain to come. 
Because sometimes life is painful. 
Sometimes it snows. 
Sometimes friends are unfaithful. 
Sometimes bones crack and hearts break.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But sometimes children smile and hold your hand. 
Sometimes wives laugh and give another chance. 
Sometimes you can turn snow into a snowman or disappear in a camping cabin up north for a few weeks. 
Sometimes there are such beautiful moments that you forget the sad ones for a bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And always, God is faithful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Always, God will walk through the storm with you, keeping the storm outside of you. 
Always, God will meet your needs. 
Always, God will ensure that every pain can have a purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And when we get through this period we call life, we can walk into His open arms and our real Life will begin. 
And then, our joy won’t come in moments. 
It will be a lasting all-consuming reality, and our pains will all slip away…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But that’s not today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, I pray that Abba will fill your heart with peace, and flood your body with healing. 
Today I pray that your surgeon is getting ready for a good night’s sleep. 
Today I pray that the weather allows you to get safely to the hospital without further stress or injury. 
And today, I pray that tomorrow will be good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breathe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;God’s got this. God’s got you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just trust Him.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">I have a friend whose husband is having surgery tomorrow. This one is for him.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Finding the Words</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/daily%20life/2019/01/16/finding-the-words.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Finding the Words" /><published>2019-01-16T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/daily%20life/2019/01/16/finding-the-words</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/daily%20life/2019/01/16/finding-the-words.html">&lt;p&gt;Happy Wednesday!
With this post, I will have met one of my goals for 2019: to post more days than I did last year. 
I’ve also eaten dairy, gluten, and sugar free for 16 days. 
Today’s supper was a bowl of gluten free vegetable pasta with sugar free tomato sauce and dairy free ‘parmesan’ cheese, followed up with a bowl of chocolate/peanut butter coconut milk icecream. 
I walked on the treadmill, spent some time decluttering old papers, and watched the last of the Tom Baker Dr. Who’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I didn’t work on my doctorate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I actually haven’t worked on that for a couple of days. 
(And, yes, I’m using a ‘couple of days’ to mean a very long time). 
Because even though I usually love playing with letters and words, some days, I just can’t find the words.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those are often the days that I wish I had been blessed with musical talents of some kind. 
If I could play the violin or whistle a tune, surely I could get my thoughts across. 
But my gifting only involves wordsmithing. 
And some days the words don’t cooperate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can totally understand the frustration of the second grader who snaps his pencil and shreds his papers. 
He’s got so much tangled up inside that he wants me to know – but the words aren’t cooperating. 
She’s got so much overwhelming emotion stuffed into that little three foot frame but she doesn’t yet know how to harness the magic of scratching a pencil across a piece of paper to make the world feel better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because it is magical – reading the right words at the right time. 
Hearing someone else say exactly what your own heart is feeling. 
Knowing that no matter how alone you may feel, you really aren’t. 
The right words can make strangers feel like family. 
The right words can erase fear, and spread peace like wildfire on a dry, windy day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, sometimes, I just can’t find the words.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes there are no words. 
The feelings are just too overwhelmingly wordless.
The pain is too present or the joy is too sweet. 
To corral it with words would oversimplify it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But sometimes you know there are words, there’s just an empty white wall standing in your way. 
The perfect words are neatly stacked up on the other side of that block but you can’t quite get to them. 
I’ve seen my second graders come up against that wall. 
The clock ticks louder and louder and the blank white wall looms overhead impervious to their attempts to graffiti on it.&lt;br /&gt;
Often there are tears of frustration, emergency bathroom breaks, and trips to the nurse. 
None of which really help. 
They just get you away from the wall for a bit and distract you from thinking about the words waiting on the other side. 
Though sometimes, while you’re focusing on those other tasks, the words return.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s where I am with my doctorate right now. 
I know the words are there. 
And I know that at some point I’ll get over the wall to where they are. 
But I also know that right now, there are a zillion things that it’s absolutely imperative that I be doing that don’t involve typing on a keyboard.
Like laundry. 
I really should go do a load of laundry…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, again, happy Wednesday. 
Congratulations on the goals you’ve met and on all of your successes. 
And as for the things you haven’t succeeded at yet, just keep plugging along. 
It’s going to be so worth it in the end!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">Happy Wednesday! With this post, I will have met one of my goals for 2019: to post more days than I did last year. I’ve also eaten dairy, gluten, and sugar free for 16 days. Today’s supper was a bowl of gluten free vegetable pasta with sugar free tomato sauce and dairy free ‘parmesan’ cheese, followed up with a bowl of chocolate/peanut butter coconut milk icecream. I walked on the treadmill, spent some time decluttering old papers, and watched the last of the Tom Baker Dr. Who’s.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Now</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/poetry/2019/01/15/now.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Now" /><published>2019-01-15T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/poetry/2019/01/15/now</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/poetry/2019/01/15/now.html">&lt;p&gt;God is the timekeeper&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keeping track of the minutes and seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That make up my time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He chose the exact pinpoint in history&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To begin my life,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And He’s chosen the second miniscule moment&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That will mark the end of my journey here&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the beginning of my journey there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wonder how He feels&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When He watches me wasting minutes,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Killing time,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Loosing seconds&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;hours&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;days&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To trivial wasteful pursuits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number of my heartbeats&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has already been counted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can I really afford to let any more of them echo past&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In unfocused waiting&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wandering&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Worrying&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wasting?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I must capture each minute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I should seize every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will name each moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting with Now.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">God is the timekeeper</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Answered Prayers</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/devotional/2019/01/14/answered-prayer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Answered Prayers" /><published>2019-01-14T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-14T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/devotional/2019/01/14/answered-prayer</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/devotional/2019/01/14/answered-prayer.html">&lt;p&gt;Some days it’s tough to crawl out of bed in the morning.&lt;br /&gt;
And some days, it’s tough to put down the book and get up off the couch. 
But I think for me, the hardest challenge is to turn off the hot water and get out of the shower. 
In the winter, the bathroom always feels chilly after the hot shower water and I dread the transition. 
Of course, I could always turn up the bathroom heat, but then I never remember to turn it back down. 
It’s kind of like turning off the oven after baking. 
But that’s a different story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This morning I was running a bit late, but I still lingered in the shower. 
Finally, I sent up an arrow prayer to God, “Help me get out!” as I twisted the shower knob a little bit higher. 
Only, I accidentally twisted the knob in the wrong direction.
As the water suddenly got colder, I very quickly hopped out of the shower.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prayer answered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not exactly how I expected it to be. 
But answered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can say that about a lot of my answered prayers. 
Not exactly how I expected, but answered. 
I’m sure that’s what I’ll be able to say one day about my currently unanswered prayers. 
Because they will all be answered one day. 
Most definitely not how I’m expecting, though…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, I prayed for patience and I got the most vocal, energetic, and emotional class I’ve ever taught. 
I’ve earned each iota of my patience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My grandfather prayed for a closer relationship between my brother and I – and I ended up spending a lot of healing time on his couch when recovering from some of my surgeries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s also the day I looked in my closet and told God I needed some new clothes. 
That evening a friend handed me a bag of clothes she’d decided to get rid of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All three of those prayers were answered in unexpected ways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember a Sunday School teacher once telling me that there are three answers to every prayer: Yes, no, and wait. 
Every time you bring a request to God, He’ll respond with one of those three. 
But I think there’s a fourth answer. 
I think sometimes, God whispers back down, “Open your eyes and look around.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When John the Baptist was in prison, he began to question why was he still in prison if his cousin Jesus was really the Christ. 
He sent his disciples to ask Jesus if he was the one, or if they should be looking for someone else. 
Jesus answered, “Go and tell John what you hear and see: the blind receive their sight and the lame walk, the lepers are cleansed and the deaf hear, and the dead are raised up, and the poor have good news preached to them” (Matthew 11:4-5). 
I wonder what John thought when they brought that answer back to him. 
Because even with all those miracles, he was still in prison.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, maybe that’s not what he was thinking. 
Maybe he focused on the miracles. 
Maybe he focused on the work Jesus was doing, on the healing and the preaching.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I prayed for patience, not only did my students teach me patience. 
They also filled my heart with joy and taught me how to be a better teacher than I ever thought I could be. 
My days on my brother’s couch brought me closer to his whole family. 
That bag of clothes from my friend filled me with excitement and encouraged me to fill a bag of my own extras and pass them on again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;God goes above and beyond with His answers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So keep asking. 
And if you don’t get an immediate yes or no, the answer could be Wait. 
But it could also be, Look. 
Look around you and see the unexpected answers. 
It could be as simple as a splash of cold water in the shower, or as complicated as a cancer diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somehow, it’s all part of His plan.
And trust me, it’s gonna be a good one!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">Some days it’s tough to crawl out of bed in the morning. And some days, it’s tough to put down the book and get up off the couch. But I think for me, the hardest challenge is to turn off the hot water and get out of the shower. In the winter, the bathroom always feels chilly after the hot shower water and I dread the transition. Of course, I could always turn up the bathroom heat, but then I never remember to turn it back down. It’s kind of like turning off the oven after baking. But that’s a different story.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Peaceful Simplicity</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/daily%20life/2019/01/13/peaceful-simplicity.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Peaceful Simplicity" /><published>2019-01-13T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/daily%20life/2019/01/13/peaceful-simplicity</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/daily%20life/2019/01/13/peaceful-simplicity.html">&lt;p&gt;Trending on Netflix, there’s a show called Tidying Up. 
It features Marie Kondo, a ‘tidying expert.’ 
I read her book, &lt;strong&gt;The Life-Changing Magic of Tidying Up&lt;/strong&gt;, last year and I’ve been enjoying her show. 
According to Marie, the first step to decluttering is to find out why you want to. 
Create a vision that you want to achieve, and then ask yourself why you want to reach that vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My vision is to have a clean house, where there’s room for the cats to run around without breaking anything, and plenty of comfortable spaces to sit and relax. 
Where there are lots of good books to read, and artifacts from around the world to look at and touch without worrying about knocking something else of a shelf. 
Where people feel comfortable, warm, and safe. 
That was the easy part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was harder to find the why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For years now, I’ve been searching for simplicity.&lt;br /&gt;
I want to live a simpler life. 
I don’t like messy and complicated. 
I don’t like the stressful feelings from having more responsibilities than fit in the 24 hours I’m given each day. 
I don’t like puzzles and problems that feel unsolvable. 
I like simple and peaceful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think that’s my why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I can declutter my house and get rid of all of those things lying around that I don’t need and only surround myself with things that make me feel happy, I think it will help make my life simple and peaceful. 
By having less stuff to focus on, maybe I can focus on the important stuff more. 
I once read a quote about asceticism that pointed out that it’s not that you shouldn’t own anything, “but that nothing should own you.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Peace doesn’t come from what we own, or what we give away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the blue jeans I picked up in Budapest make me smile and I always feel happy when I’m wearing my pink cowboy boots, happiness is a fleeting emotion. 
I’m seeking a deeper emotion that sits in the bedrock of my soul and comforts me whether I’m happy or sad, hungry or full, cold or hot, lost or found. 
This feeling held me in those two years when I was little that we lived in a van traveling around New England. 
This feeling held me when I sat on the floor of an empty room remembering what it had looked like filled. 
This feeling held me when we piled into an over stuffed station wagon to leave my first home, crawled into my grandfather’s truck move to Canada, and walked onto a 747 to head to Africa. 
This feeling held me when I signed the papers and bought my own house, and it’s holding me right now as I type these words.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s what I want to be able to spend my energy focusing on. 
The Peace that passes understanding. 
I want my house to become a place of peace that others can feel when they come in through the doors. 
I want to be able to come home from a frantic, hectic, crazy, emotional, exhilarating day at work and leave it all behind on the front porch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s my why. 
I want to declutter and put my house in order so that it can become a place of peace in a chaotic world.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">Trending on Netflix, there’s a show called Tidying Up. It features Marie Kondo, a ‘tidying expert.’ I read her book, The Life-Changing Magic of Tidying Up, last year and I’ve been enjoying her show. According to Marie, the first step to decluttering is to find out why you want to. Create a vision that you want to achieve, and then ask yourself why you want to reach that vision.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day Twelve</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/daily%20life/2019/01/12/day-twelve.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day Twelve" /><published>2019-01-12T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-12T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/daily%20life/2019/01/12/day-twelve</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/daily%20life/2019/01/12/day-twelve.html">&lt;p&gt;And just like that, we’re at Day Twelve, the day most Americans give up on their resolutions.
I almost didn’t blog.
But I figured that today was not the best day to skip.
Because that’s how it happens, isn’t it?
You are doing something faithfully, every day, so you decide it won’t hurt to take just one day off.
But that one day throws off the routine and dwindles the momentum.
Somehow you never even notice when you slip off the track.
You see something six months later that reminds you of that track that you used to be on when you were more resolved.
And you wonder why you stopped…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve made a couple of resolutions this year.
I’m writing more.
I’m reading more.
I’m eating healthier.
That one is the most life-changing.
For January, I’ll stick with the dairy, gluten, and sugar free plan.
Then at the end of the month, I’ll reassess my symptoms and decide the plan for February.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s actually been fun exploring recipes and trying new ingredients.
Today I made banana/blueberry/oatmeal cookies.
And I found a recipe for ‘mac and cheese’ that I can’t wait to try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what I like most about the new lifestyle it’s forced me to adopt is the intentionality.
I’m carefully thinking through each meal and snack.
I’m planning ahead for the times I won’t be at home.
I’m setting aside large chunks of time to spend in the kitchen - and spending a lot less time mindlessly watching tv or playing on my phone.
While I can still be spontaneous and impulsive, life has fallen into a comfortable routine.
I’m feeling more productive.
This has spilled over into other areas of my life, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the process of reorganizing my time to accomodate my new kitchen activities, I set aside time for other important activites as well – like reading my Bible and chatting with Abba.
I cut out a lot of my tv time, but added in more book time.
Now I actually look forward to my alarm clock going off in the morning, because I get to read in bed for half an hour before I hop onto my treadmill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By intentionally filling my days with beneficial and enjoyable things, I’m building a lifestyle that I can (and want to!) maintain.
Which is why I’m not going to be quitting on my New Year’s Resolutions today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m eager to see what the next twelve days will bring.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">And just like that, we’re at Day Twelve, the day most Americans give up on their resolutions. I almost didn’t blog. But I figured that today was not the best day to skip. Because that’s how it happens, isn’t it? You are doing something faithfully, every day, so you decide it won’t hurt to take just one day off. But that one day throws off the routine and dwindles the momentum. Somehow you never even notice when you slip off the track. You see something six months later that reminds you of that track that you used to be on when you were more resolved. And you wonder why you stopped…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Joy</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/poetry/faith/2019/01/11/joy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Joy" /><published>2019-01-11T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/poetry/faith/2019/01/11/joy</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/poetry/faith/2019/01/11/joy.html">&lt;p&gt;The following two poems are from my second book All Is Well. 
 I wrote both poems during my cancer journey, the first shortly after diagnosis and the second after I had finished all of my cancer treatments.
 It wasn’t until a couple of years ago, when I was preparing for a poetry reading, that I discovered that the second poem shows a beautiful answer to the prayer in the first.
 God doesn’t always answer our prayers right away, and He doesn’t always give the answer we’re hoping for or expect.
 But He does always hear our prayers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy for Fear&lt;/strong&gt; (Written shortly after a cancer diagnosis)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m scared today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So much ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So much sickness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The journey is too much for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But You’ve made this path for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Help me to walk in it willingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Give me the grace&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;for each moment&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You bring me to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hold my shaking heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Send Your comfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Help me be a comfort&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to the hurting around me&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;instead of just dwelling on myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take my fear&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and give me Your joy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joy&lt;/strong&gt; (Written after a year of cancer treatments)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a joy in my heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through You. In You. Because of You.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Complete, mind-blowing, body-tingling, stabilizing joy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of Your many, many gifts to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A joy that doesn’t depend on circumstances,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;that doesn’t depend on people,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;that doesn’t depend on what mood I’m in,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;what clothes I’m wearing,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;what day it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A joy that only depends on You.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A joy that warms my heart in snowstorms,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;comforts my heart in chaos,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and cradles my heart snuggly&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;when the world is lost and confused around me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A joy that is faithful,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;enduring,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;trustworthy, and endearing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A joy that can be spread from heart to heart,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;smile to smile,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;soul to soul,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;at the whisper of Your name,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in the reading of Your word.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A joy that is more powerful than the life around me,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;that can smile through tears,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;that can hug through hate,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;that can hold on when everyone else lets go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A joy beyond understanding,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;beyond comprehension,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;beyond my wildest dreams,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;but not beyond my reach -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;because You’ve placed it within my heart.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">The following two poems are from my second book All Is Well. I wrote both poems during my cancer journey, the first shortly after diagnosis and the second after I had finished all of my cancer treatments. It wasn’t until a couple of years ago, when I was preparing for a poetry reading, that I discovered that the second poem shows a beautiful answer to the prayer in the first. God doesn’t always answer our prayers right away, and He doesn’t always give the answer we’re hoping for or expect. But He does always hear our prayers. Joy for Fear (Written shortly after a cancer diagnosis) I’m scared today. So much ahead. So much sickness. The journey is too much for me. But You’ve made this path for me. Help me to walk in it willingly. Give me the grace for each moment You bring me to. Hold my shaking heart. Send Your comfort. Help me be a comfort to the hurting around me instead of just dwelling on myself. Take my fear and give me Your joy. Joy (Written after a year of cancer treatments) There’s a joy in my heart. Through You. In You. Because of You. Complete, mind-blowing, body-tingling, stabilizing joy. One of Your many, many gifts to me. A joy that doesn’t depend on circumstances, that doesn’t depend on people, that doesn’t depend on what mood I’m in, what clothes I’m wearing, what day it is. A joy that only depends on You. A joy that warms my heart in snowstorms, comforts my heart in chaos, and cradles my heart snuggly when the world is lost and confused around me. A joy that is faithful, enduring, trustworthy, and endearing. A joy that can be spread from heart to heart, smile to smile, soul to soul, at the whisper of Your name, in the reading of Your word. A joy that is more powerful than the life around me, that can smile through tears, that can hug through hate, that can hold on when everyone else lets go. A joy beyond understanding, beyond comprehension, beyond my wildest dreams, but not beyond my reach - because You’ve placed it within my heart.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Day Ten</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/daily%20life/2019/01/10/day-ten.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day Ten" /><published>2019-01-10T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-10T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/daily%20life/2019/01/10/day-ten</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/daily%20life/2019/01/10/day-ten.html">&lt;p&gt;It’s Day Ten of the 19th year of the 21st century, and of my gluten, sugar, and dairy free diet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I passed from the I-want-to-eat-my-students’-snacks-when-they’re-not-looking phase, through the I-really-don’t-care-if-they-are-looking stage, into the yeah-that-looks-good-but-I’m-happy-with-my-own-snack stage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve found that if I stuff my lunchbox with enough healthy goodies that I have choices when I get hungry, I tend to not get food envy.
I also don’t panic that I’ll run out of food.
Today I actually had leftovers coming home with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday was my first non-work or grocery shopping excursion out into the world since going gluten free.
I had an eye doctor’s appointment.
Normally, I would have gone to the appointment, then grabbed something to eat somewhere on the way home.
But with the new diet, it’s harder to find prepared food.
So instead, I had a couple extra pumpkin cookies that I ate just before my appointment, which filled me up enough to make it home for supper instead of eating out.
I’m not only eating healthy, I’m saving money, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today was my first drag-myself-home-exhausted day since starting my new diet.
Usually, these are days when I’d pull a tv dinner out of the freezer and pop it into the microwave.
That’s not an option on my new diet.
As I drove home, I was mentally running through all of my options.
What did I have that would be simple?
Maybe a bowl of cereal with coconut milk or a piece of toast with jam?
(Coincidentally, that’s what I had for breakfast today).
Then I remembered the avocado I’d bought and never used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, today’s lazy day supper was a piece of homemade bread that I pulled out of the freezer and toasted, topped with mashed avocado, and a reheated turkey burger that I’d grilled up on Sunday.
It was quick, easy, and delicious.
The hardest part was opening the silicone freezer bag holding the bread.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I outlasted the food envy stage.
I broke the old habit of eating out after appointments.
I ate healthy when I was too tired to cook healthy.
And I’ve almost made it to day 12 - the day most Americans give up on their New Year’s resolutions.
I have high hopes for this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How are you doing on your goals and plans?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">It’s Day Ten of the 19th year of the 21st century, and of my gluten, sugar, and dairy free diet.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Just a Reminder</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/-faith/2019/01/09/just-a-reminder.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Just a Reminder" /><published>2019-01-09T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-09T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/-faith/2019/01/09/just-a-reminder</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/-faith/2019/01/09/just-a-reminder.html">&lt;p&gt;I just wanted to remind you that you are loved.
More than loved.
You are absolutely cherished.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you know Him or not, the God Who created the world and holds it in His hands, loves you.
Whether you believe in Him or not, the Spirit who knows your best hidden secrets, loves you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Undeniably.
Unmeasurably.
Unfailingly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And His love is not dependent on what you do.
It doesn’t change based on what you did - when no one was looking, or when a whole crowd was watching.
He simply loves you because you are you.
No matter who you are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter who you are.
No matter who you want to be. 
No matter who you wish you were.
No matter where you go.
No matter who you go with.
No matter why you go there.
No matter what you do.
No matter what you didn’t do.
No matter what was done to you.
No matter… You matter!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are loved.
More than you can ever understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just wanted to remind you…&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">I just wanted to remind you that you are loved. More than loved. You are absolutely cherished.</summary></entry></feed>