<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-12-30T16:09:14-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Scribbling Hope</title><subtitle>Sometimes we don’t get to choose. Sometimes God grabs our hands and leads us on a journey. One we may not understand. One we would not have chosen. But one that shapes, changes, and saves our lives. Because He is merciful. Because He loves us.</subtitle><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><entry><title type="html">Stella’s Sleeping</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/04/28/stellas-sleeping/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Stella's Sleeping" /><published>2018-04-28T11:52:02-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-28T11:52:02-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/04/28/stellas-sleeping</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/04/28/stellas-sleeping/">&lt;p&gt;Stella’s sleeping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She’s lying in the library between a bookshelf and the rocking chair, with her head down on the carpet and a paw draped over her eyes. And she’s sleeping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been a while since I saw her asleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been a while since she laid her head down and relaxed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About five weeks ago, I looked at her and suddenly realized that she looked old. She seemed thin and wobbled a little when she walked across the ledge in front of the tv. So I scheduled an appointment with her vet and we stuck her (kicking and caterwauling) into her carrier and went for a ride. The vet knew something was wrong – by this time she had developed lesions all over her face and her weight loss was dramatic. We just didn’t know what. She ran a couple of tests that all came back negative, and we decided to try a round of antibiotics and prednisone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lesions cleared up almost immediately, and her appetite improved. But as soon as she finished the first round of antibiotics, the lesions came back all over body. The vet ran a couple of new tests, but again it all came back negative. However, we knew something was wrong and we knew it was very likely something big.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We put her back on the antibiotics for another two weeks. Twice a day I’d scoop her up in a towel to hold her flaying limbs while mom gave her a couple of licks of cream before slipping a pill down her throat. We got better at getting the pill down her mouth on the first try, but she hasn’t really improved her score on the graceful dismount when I try to set her back down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She next developed the sniffles, which soon became a sneezy, drippy, runny-nosed cold, so we put her back on the steroids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the meds ran out last week, we went in for another visit with the vet. By this time, we could clearly see what that “something big” was. Her stomach was bloating, and she had a mass on her liver. My little diva has liver cancer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Now we know,” said the vet, with tears in her eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I brought her home to love on her. She gets a prednisone a day – they’ll suppress the side effects of the cancer for a bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the first time in her life, my precious diva who’s had almost as many homes as I have, has carte blanche to eat anything she wants. I made her buffets of tempting tidbits and fed her every time she raced me to the kitchen. When I got home from work, I visited her in the library and rubbed her scabbed, furry head. On warm afternoons, I opened the balcony door and let her sit in the fresh air and the sunshine. I think she’s happy. But she’s also been restless. She’s hungry, but having trouble eating. Now she’s down to mostly just licking up tuna juice and sauces. Yesterday she started having trouble holding anything down and we weren’t able to give her the steroid. It’s almost time to let her go…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Letting go can be so terrifyingly difficult, can’t it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our furry friends are family members. Loving, kind, loyal critters who keep you company in your darkest moments when you don’t want anyone around but don’t want to be alone. Who lower your blood pressure and run to meet you when you come home. I miss that. I’ll miss her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know there will be animals in Heaven. I’m praying that my Stella Belle will be one of them. I’m grateful that my Abba is in control.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">Stella’s sleeping. She’s lying in the library between a bookshelf and the rocking chair, with her head down on the carpet and a paw draped over her eyes. And she’s sleeping.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Valentine (previously published in part under the title Yes)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/02/14/my-valentine-previously-published-in-part-under-the-title-yes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Valentine (previously published in part under the title Yes)" /><published>2018-02-14T16:48:16-05:00</published><updated>2018-02-14T16:48:16-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/02/14/my-valentine-previously-published-in-part-under-the-title-yes</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/02/14/my-valentine-previously-published-in-part-under-the-title-yes/">&lt;p&gt;Valentine’s Day can be a tough day for some people. If you’re in a relationship, there’s pressure to get the perfect gift and go on the perfect date. If you’re not in a relationship, every ad and candy heart reminds you that you’re alone, hinting that, maybe, somehow, you’re flawed because of that aloneness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m one of the many who are not in a relationship. And most of the time, that’s not a bad thing. But sometimes, like on Valentine’s Day, I start contemplating the ‘What if’s and ‘Why not’s of life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One year, in desperation, I finally sat down and had a long talk with my Abba about it. I ended our conversation with the question, “Will You be my Valentine?” And this was His answer. I thought I’d share it with you, in case you’re looking for the perfect Valentine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;span style=&quot;font-size: x-large;&quot;&gt;Yes.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;span style=&quot;font-size: large;&quot;&gt;Infinite, omnipotent, stretch-my-arms-out-and-die-for-you yes.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;span style=&quot;font-size: large;&quot;&gt;I will be your &lt;span style=&quot;font-size: x-large;&quot;&gt;Valentine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;span style=&quot;font-size: small;&quot;&gt;I invented time itself so I could spend it with you.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;span style=&quot;font-size: small;&quot;&gt;I created your heart so you could feel My love.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;span style=&quot;font-size: small;&quot;&gt;I grew mountains just so you could laugh your way up them. &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will be your Hope in this broken world.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will be your Light in the middle of the darkest nights.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  Your Warmth through the coldest winter days.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  Your Comfort in the MRI tubes.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  Your Companion on the radiation tables.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will ask the flowers to bloom by the side of the road to catch your eye and make you smile as you drive to work. I will cause dust and debris to travel through space and momentarily block a far off sun just to make a star twinkle when you glance up at the night sky. I will sit beside you on the airplane, and I will breathe a wind under its wings to get you safely where I want you to be. I will drop blankets of snow to cancel school and give you more time to spend with Me.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will hold your hand in public.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  And I&amp;#8217;ll hold your heart in private.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I&amp;#8217;ll hold all of your fears, worries, insecurities, sadnesses, and uglies in the palm of My Almighty Hand.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will love you every single second of your life from before your conception until after your death. When you&amp;#8217;re happy, when you&amp;#8217;re angry, when you&amp;#8217;re living in denial or in sin &amp;#8212; just as much as when you&amp;#8217;re loving me right back as much as your human heart can understand.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will never leave you.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will never forsake you.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will never turn my back.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will never let you down.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  And I&amp;#8217;ll wait patiently for you to come home when you turn your back on Me.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will always understand.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will always listen.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will always forgive.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will always be there &amp;#8212; beside you, behind you, before you, within you.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will love you exactly as you are, and I will do everything possible to make you more You.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will screen your calls &amp;#8212; blocking all unnecessary pain. I will help you carry the burdens that will bring you closer to me.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will give you such great gifts. Everyday new mercies and blessings.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  With me life will be a Surprise.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  With me life will be Good.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will do more for you than you could ever ask or imagine.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;color: #990000; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  I will be your Valentine.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;span style=&quot;color: #990000;&quot;&gt;Thank you for asking.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">Valentine’s Day can be a tough day for some people. If you’re in a relationship, there’s pressure to get the perfect gift and go on the perfect date. If you’re not in a relationship, every ad and candy heart reminds you that you’re alone, hinting that, maybe, somehow, you’re flawed because of that aloneness.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Story About a Car</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/02/03/a-story-about-a-car/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Story About a Car" /><published>2018-02-03T16:20:38-05:00</published><updated>2018-02-03T16:20:38-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/02/03/a-story-about-a-car</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/02/03/a-story-about-a-car/">&lt;p&gt;Mom and Dad have a friend that owns a used car dealership. They’ve bought many cars from him, so a couple of Saturdays ago, they brought me by to chat with him. I tried to describe what I wanted. I told him that I’d tried a Nissan but it was too small, and I’d tried a Jeep Grand Cherokee and found it too big. I really wasn’t happy with any car I looked at because it just wasn’t my Rav. “You want a Rav?” he asked me. “I can get you a Rav.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we talked, we discussed prices and options and non-negotiables. Then he told me that he was going to go to an auction that Friday and he’d look for a car for me. I finally made it through that week – patience is something God is still working on in me – and called him back on Friday afternoon. “I’m really sorry,” he said. “There just isn’t much in your price range.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Discouraged, I hung up the phone and spent the rest of the day on my laptop browsing the inventory of used car lots in my area. He was right. There weren’t many options within three thousand dollars of my price range. Finally, I sat down and had a talk with God about it. I knew He had a car for me. I just didn’t know what I had to let go of for it. Would I have to increase my car-buying budget? Would I have to accept that it might not be as cute as my Rav? Would I need to give in and get something white or blue? Or, even worse, would I have to wait? I was already certain that I’d have to give up my hope for a manual transmission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every January for the past couple of years, I’ve gone on a spending freeze. It helps me reset (and sometimes recover from overspending for Christmas). It reminds me to reprioritize and think about what things I truly need. As I prayed, I decided that I would continue my no-spend January and wait until February to purchase a car. I also decided that I didn’t absolutely need a black suv. It could be a different color. It could be a different type of vehicle. I just needed something affordable to drive until I finished grad school and paid off the solar panel loans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, I sat on my living room floor by the fire and filed my taxes. Then I dug through my budget and looked for columns I could pilfer from to beef up my car-buying fund. I also counted up all of the money I’d saved by not shopping for the month of January. By doing all of this, I was able to increase my car fund by almost four thousand dollars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, Mom, Dad, and I hopped into Dad’s PT Cruiser and drove back to the used car lot. The first car I saw in the lot was an adorable red Hyundai Tuscan. It was a 2006 with 118,000 miles. There was also a red Ford Escape, some silver suvs, and a bunch of other vehicles half buried under snow and ice. We slipped our way across the icy lot and into his office and I asked him what he had available in my new price range. He began talking about the Ford Escape. It was priced a little higher, but he thought we could make it work. I asked him what else he had in that price range, and he named a couple of other vehicles. I’m not sure which one of us asked about the Tuscan, but his immediate response was, “Oh that? I’ll give you that for thirty-five hundred.” I almost shook his hand and bought it there and then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then he shook his head. “But there’s a problem.” My heart clenched as I began pondering worst-case scenarios: it doesn’t run or it needs extensive repairs. But here’s where God stepped in. Because what the seller thought was a problem was actually God reminding me that He does care about the details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But there’s a problem,” he said. “It’s a standard transmission.” He didn’t know that when he bought it at the auction. I smiled and reached for the keys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He handed me a dealer license plate. We opened the back window and propped up the plate, then drove around the block and down the highway for a bit. It’s not my Rav, but it’ll make a fine road trip companion. I signed the paperwork and handed over a down payment. We sat around talking, laughing, and praying for a half hour after that. On Monday they’ll swing by to pick up my Rav. On Tuesday I’ll drive the New One home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So to recap, I got the manual transmission compact suv I’d been hoping for, though I did budge a bit on the color. &lt;em&gt;And&lt;/em&gt;, the car, the two-year warranty, and the registration fees all added up to just under two thousand dollars below my &lt;em&gt;original&lt;/em&gt; budget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah, our God cares about the little things, too.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">Mom and Dad have a friend that owns a used car dealership. They’ve bought many cars from him, so a couple of Saturdays ago, they brought me by to chat with him. I tried to describe what I wanted. I told him that I’d tried a Nissan but it was too small, and I’d tried a Jeep Grand Cherokee and found it too big. I really wasn’t happy with any car I looked at because it just wasn’t my Rav. “You want a Rav?” he asked me. “I can get you a Rav.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Still Writing</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/30/still-writing/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Still Writing" /><published>2018-01-29T20:46:58-05:00</published><updated>2018-01-29T20:46:58-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/30/still-writing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/30/still-writing/">&lt;p&gt;So I’ve had a lot of people ask me what my next book will be about. I love that people expect there to be a next one. There will be – I still have so much left to say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what will it be about?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, one idea is to write a fiction book about a first year teacher. Over my years in a classroom, I’ve collected a few stories that people outside of the classroom might find a tad bit surprising. You teachers know what I’m talking about. Just at lunch today we were taking about the time a I had a student swallow a penny during math class. I immediately sent him to the nurse who emptied his pockets and took all of his money. He came back, sat down, and took off his shoe. Pulling out another penny, he calmly said, “She didn’t take this one,” as he put it into his mouth. I’ve got lots of stories like that which might make for a fun book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also still want to do something with my son’s journal from the two weeks he spent on the streets in Lynn. I learned a lot from that experience and I would like to share it. Oh – and I want to write a children’s book that I can share with my students.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are so many ideas and so many blank pages to fill with words.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any suggestions?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">So I’ve had a lot of people ask me what my next book will be about. I love that people expect there to be a next one. There will be – I still have so much left to say.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">from Day 18 in Join Me In The Journey</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/22/from-day-18-in-join-me-in-the-journey/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="from Day 18 in Join Me In The Journey" /><published>2018-01-22T03:33:43-05:00</published><updated>2018-01-22T03:33:43-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/22/from-day-18-in-join-me-in-the-journey</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/22/from-day-18-in-join-me-in-the-journey/">&lt;p&gt;Sometimes the tragedies in our lives are a direct result of something we did. Sometimes it is our fault. But often, there doesn’t seem to be a reason.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Jesus’ time, people just assumed that bad things were sin related.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Jesus was walking along, he saw a man who had been blind from birth. “Teacher,” his disciples asked him, “why was this man born blind? Was it a result of his own sins or those of his parents?” (John 9:1-2)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their question wasn’t why was the man blind, but whose sin caused it. Jesus gave them a different answer and a different perspective on tragedy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It was not because of his sins or his parents’ sins,” Jesus answered. “He was born blind so the power of God could be seen in him…” Then he spit on the ground, made mud with the saliva, and smoothed the mud over the blind man’s eyes. He told him, “Go and wash in the pool of Siloam” (Siloam means sent). So the man went and washed, and came back seeing! (John 9:3, 6-7)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The disciples were looking backward for the cause, but Jesus was looking forward to all the good that would come out of it…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes our pain and our tragedies are meant to turn us back to Him. Sometimes, they point Him out to someone else who’s searching for an answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes the tragedy is simply an excuse for God to step in with a mighty miracle to give the world one more opportunity to believe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">Sometimes the tragedies in our lives are a direct result of something we did. Sometimes it is our fault. But often, there doesn’t seem to be a reason.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On the Hunt</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/21/on-the-hunt/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On the Hunt" /><published>2018-01-21T11:20:36-05:00</published><updated>2018-01-21T11:20:36-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/21/on-the-hunt</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/21/on-the-hunt/">&lt;p&gt;This is going to be harder than I thought…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I went car shopping. The plan was to pick up something cheap and pay cash for it. I don’t want to finance right now because I’m only two years into my house mortgage and I’m still taking out school loans for my grad program. I stepped onto the lot with no preconceived ideas of what I wanted. I was going to be flexible and open to whatever was available. At least, that was the plan…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first dealership we went to was closed, but we walked around and looked at the cars. There were blue ones, red ones, white ones, and silver ones. As I looked around I realized that my heart is set on a black one. I did see two cars that I would consider and we decided to come back when the lot was open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second lot seemed more high end. There were more cars than in the first lot and no red rust spots around the wheels. The dealer tried to keep a straight face when I told him my price range then went into the back to search through his inventory. He brought us around the back of the building to a little black Nissan. I took a quick look at it and immediately realized that I also want an SUV. I shook my head and said no thank you — I need something easier to get in and out of. On the trek back to our ride, we passed a couple of RAV4 s and I was very tempted to ask their prices. But I kept walking. The dealer must have asked me three times if I was sure I wouldn’t consider financing. I’m sure. God’s got the perfect car at the perfect price set aside for me. I just need to find it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the way to the third dealership, I mentally dug through my budget and realized that I could safely increase my price range. I started with my original price range, then said I could be flexible. He clicked around on his computer for a few minutes, then grabbed a set of keys and brought me to the black Jeep Grand Cherokee in the center of his lot. He started it up with the remote starter and talked about the built in navigation system. I was very excited, but as I crawled up into the driver seat, I realized that I want a compact SUV. I sat there for a second while my dad inspected the outside and my mom asked how many miles it had. Then I hopped out and told the dealer that it was just too big. I left him my name and number in case he found something that would meet my criteria.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, to recap I am going pay cash for a cheaper vehicle that will get me through the rest of my doctoral program. I am going to be open and flexible on what that car will be. My only non-negotiables are that it needs to be a black compact SUV. How hard can it be?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">This is going to be harder than I thought…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The End of an Era</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/17/the-end-of-an-era/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The End of an Era" /><published>2018-01-17T12:15:25-05:00</published><updated>2018-01-17T12:15:25-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/17/the-end-of-an-era</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/17/the-end-of-an-era/">&lt;p&gt;Ry Junior, my 2003 Toyota Rav4, gave me his all yesterday. Down to his last gear, unable to accelerate past ten mph and screaming like a freight train, he put-putted me into my work parking lot. He was definitely the little engine that could, faithfully putting his metal heart and soul into that last mile and sighing with relief and satisfaction at a job well done when I turned the key left for the last time. Well done, Faithful Steed. Well done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ry Jr. came to live with us in 2003 with 62 miles on his treads. He moved in when his older brother, Ry the Silver Rav, moved out. While Ry was front wheel drive, Ry Jr. was a brave and energetic all wheel drive, eager to meet my family’s needs. He loved frolicking in the snow, driving fast on the highway, and exploring new parking places all over the country. Although not quite tardis technology like his friend the red SMART car, he had easily removed back seats and plenty of room to accommodate for my shopping sprees and road trips.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ry Jr. accompanied me on three cross-country road trips. He’s been to 47 states and Canada, though Massachusetts was always his favorite. While he never fulfilled his life-long dream of driving to Alaska, he put in 210,889 miles and earned his rest. Now it’s time for someone else to drive him around for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ry Jr.’s health began to fail when his muffler rusted through and fell off. He dragged it to Midas who soldered it back on and warned that the end might be in sight. Two years ago, after a fairly expensive fix, the mechanic sadly shook his head and said that this would be the last feasible fix. He promised his mcgyvering would get us through the summer and maybe through the fall. Shortly after that, Ry Jr. lost fifth gear somewhere down in North Carolina. But he kept on running through that summer and fall, and the next summer and the next fall. Until yesterday, when he gave up three more gears to get me safely to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ry Jr. leaves behind in his parking lot the red SMART car and a PT cruiser, neither of which have the same heart, good looks, or ability to drive in the snow. He also leaves behind a mournful operator who will always remember the cute car that always got her where she needed to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you, Ry Jr. We had some bumps and bruises, but I’ll readily admit that they were all due to operator errors. Even at the very end, you always got me from a to b. You were loved and you will be missed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;gallery-1&quot; class=&quot;gallery galleryid-359 gallery-columns-3 gallery-size-thumbnail&quot;&gt;
  &lt;figure class=&quot;gallery-item&quot;&gt; 
  
  &lt;div class=&quot;gallery-icon landscape&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;http://box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/2018/01/17/the-end-of-an-era/at-the-freedom-stone/&quot;&gt;&lt;img width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; src=&quot;https://i1.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/at-the-freedom-stone.jpg?resize=150%2C150&quot; class=&quot;attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; srcset=&quot;https://i1.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/at-the-freedom-stone.jpg?resize=150%2C150 150w, https://i1.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/at-the-freedom-stone.jpg?zoom=2&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 300w, https://i1.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/at-the-freedom-stone.jpg?zoom=3&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 450w&quot; sizes=&quot;(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px&quot; data-recalc-dims=&quot;1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;gallery-item&quot;&gt; 
  
  &lt;div class=&quot;gallery-icon landscape&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;http://box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/2018/01/17/the-end-of-an-era/at-the-new-house/&quot;&gt;&lt;img width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; src=&quot;https://i1.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/at-the-new-house.jpg?resize=150%2C150&quot; class=&quot;attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; srcset=&quot;https://i1.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/at-the-new-house.jpg?resize=150%2C150 150w, https://i1.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/at-the-new-house.jpg?zoom=2&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 300w, https://i1.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/at-the-new-house.jpg?zoom=3&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 450w&quot; sizes=&quot;(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px&quot; data-recalc-dims=&quot;1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;gallery-item&quot;&gt; 
  
  &lt;div class=&quot;gallery-icon landscape&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;http://box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/2018/01/17/the-end-of-an-era/camping-out/&quot;&gt;&lt;img width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; src=&quot;https://i1.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/camping-out.jpg?resize=150%2C150&quot; class=&quot;attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; srcset=&quot;https://i1.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/camping-out.jpg?resize=150%2C150 150w, https://i1.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/camping-out.jpg?zoom=2&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 300w, https://i1.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/camping-out.jpg?zoom=3&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 450w&quot; sizes=&quot;(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px&quot; data-recalc-dims=&quot;1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;gallery-item&quot;&gt; 
  
  &lt;div class=&quot;gallery-icon landscape&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;http://box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/2018/01/17/the-end-of-an-era/olympus-digital-camera/&quot;&gt;&lt;img width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; src=&quot;https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/hailstorm.jpg?resize=150%2C150&quot; class=&quot;attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; aria-describedby=&quot;gallery-1-363&quot; srcset=&quot;https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/hailstorm.jpg?resize=150%2C150 150w, https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/hailstorm.jpg?zoom=2&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 300w, https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/hailstorm.jpg?zoom=3&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 450w&quot; sizes=&quot;(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px&quot; data-recalc-dims=&quot;1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&quot;wp-caption-text gallery-caption&quot; id=&quot;gallery-1-363&quot;&gt; OLYMPUS DIGITAL CAMERA &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;gallery-item&quot;&gt; 
  
  &lt;div class=&quot;gallery-icon portrait&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;http://box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/2018/01/17/the-end-of-an-era/in-snow/&quot;&gt;&lt;img width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; src=&quot;https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/in-snow.jpg?resize=150%2C150&quot; class=&quot;attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; srcset=&quot;https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/in-snow.jpg?resize=150%2C150 150w, https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/in-snow.jpg?zoom=2&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 300w, https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/in-snow.jpg?zoom=3&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 450w&quot; sizes=&quot;(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px&quot; data-recalc-dims=&quot;1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;gallery-item&quot;&gt; 
  
  &lt;div class=&quot;gallery-icon landscape&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;http://box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/2018/01/17/the-end-of-an-era/out-west/&quot;&gt;&lt;img width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; src=&quot;https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/out-west.jpg?resize=150%2C150&quot; class=&quot;attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; srcset=&quot;https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/out-west.jpg?resize=150%2C150 150w, https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/out-west.jpg?zoom=2&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 300w, https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/out-west.jpg?zoom=3&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 450w&quot; sizes=&quot;(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px&quot; data-recalc-dims=&quot;1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;gallery-item&quot;&gt; 
  
  &lt;div class=&quot;gallery-icon landscape&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;http://box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/2018/01/17/the-end-of-an-era/road-trip-2/&quot;&gt;&lt;img width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; src=&quot;https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/road-trip.jpg?resize=150%2C150&quot; class=&quot;attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; srcset=&quot;https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/road-trip.jpg?resize=150%2C150 150w, https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/road-trip.jpg?zoom=2&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 300w, https://i2.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/road-trip.jpg?zoom=3&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 450w&quot; sizes=&quot;(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px&quot; data-recalc-dims=&quot;1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;gallery-item&quot;&gt; 
  
  &lt;div class=&quot;gallery-icon portrait&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;http://box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/2018/01/17/the-end-of-an-era/watching-the-goose-unicylce/&quot;&gt;&lt;img width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; src=&quot;https://i0.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/watching-the-goose-unicylce.jpg?resize=150%2C150&quot; class=&quot;attachment-thumbnail size-thumbnail&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; srcset=&quot;https://i0.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/watching-the-goose-unicylce.jpg?resize=150%2C150 150w, https://i0.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/watching-the-goose-unicylce.jpg?zoom=2&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 300w, https://i0.wp.com/box5518.temp.domains/~scribbv7/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/watching-the-goose-unicylce.jpg?zoom=3&amp;amp;resize=150%2C150 450w&quot; sizes=&quot;(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px&quot; data-recalc-dims=&quot;1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">Ry Junior, my 2003 Toyota Rav4, gave me his all yesterday. Down to his last gear, unable to accelerate past ten mph and screaming like a freight train, he put-putted me into my work parking lot. He was definitely the little engine that could, faithfully putting his metal heart and soul into that last mile and sighing with relief and satisfaction at a job well done when I turned the key left for the last time. Well done, Faithful Steed. Well done.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Join Me In The Journey</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/15/join-me-in-the-journey/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Join Me In The Journey" /><published>2018-01-15T11:38:07-05:00</published><updated>2018-01-15T11:38:07-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/15/join-me-in-the-journey</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/15/join-me-in-the-journey/">&lt;p&gt;It’s finished! Book three: Join Me In the Journey is finally ready to publish and will be available on Amazon in three to five business days. Here’s an except from the introduction:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As I’m sitting here writing this book, I’m wishing you were sitting here with me. Wouldn’t it be nice to chat over a cup of hot chocolate and share our thoughts on life? To give and take, and grow, together? That’s the purpose of this book. It’s a chance to share, to reflect, and to grow.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I wrote In His Hands to share about God’s goodness, grace, and love during my cancer journey, and to maybe take a bit of fear from the world. My second book, All Is Well, is a collection of the poems that came from that journey. After reading those books, a few people approached me and commented on my faith and how nice it was that I could have such peace.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This book is an invitation.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;You can rest in His hands, too.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;For some reason, for some purpose, God carefully crafted us to be exactly who we are. Oh, we’re not done yet. I know I have a couple of corners that He’s still scrubbing at. Maybe you do, too?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;But here we are, cherished and unique.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;For the next 31 days, let’s celebrate our uniqueness by reflecting on who we are, who God is, and why He made us. It’ll only take about 10 minutes a day…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, keep an eye out on Amazon! I can’t wait to hear what you think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">It’s finished! Book three: Join Me In the Journey is finally ready to publish and will be available on Amazon in three to five business days. Here’s an except from the introduction:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Just Let Go</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/09/just-let-go/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Just Let Go" /><published>2018-01-09T18:44:24-05:00</published><updated>2018-01-09T18:44:24-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/09/just-let-go</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/09/just-let-go/">&lt;p&gt;I’ve always liked having a lot of stuff around me. I think it started when I was a missionary kid living in Africa where it was harder to get many things. I’d save up my allowance each week, and on those every other year trips to the United States, I’d blow it all on clothes and candy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or maybe it started even earlier than that, when I was nine and my parents first became missionaries, when I had to downsize all of my worldly possessions into a suitcase and a trunk. I can remember when a huge blue dumpster was parked in our driveway. It’s amazing how quickly a family of four can fill a dumpster. Toys, books, papers, clothes – everything had to be sifted through and sorted into three categories: dragged around the world with us, stored in the church attic, or let go. Furniture was trashed, sold or donated. A lot of items were sold at a yard sale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One day, I stood on the deck and watched my father toss our mattresses over the railing into the dumpster. They slowly flipped over on the way down and landed with a hollow thud. I walked back into my bedroom and looked around. It was empty, completely empty, with the closet doors open wide. I sat down on the floor, remembering the clothes and toys that used to be inside that closet. The desk was gone. The bed was gone. All of my stuff was gone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The four of us piled into an overstuffed station wagon, waved to the neighbors, and drove away. Shortly after that, Mom and Dad bought a van. For the next two years, we spent a lot of time in that van, traveling from church to church, from guesthouse to guesthouse, raising support and gathering up supporters. We lived in Charlton, Massachusetts for a couple of months, and stayed in Barrington, Rhode Island for a while. Some of my stuffed animals traveled with us, along with a handful of books. Dad made a box that fit between the two back seats in the van. A thin board divided it – half was mine and half was for my brother. This was my space, my place, where I kept my toys and treasures while we traveled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was 11, we downsized again. My stuffed animals were put in storage and we took only what would fit in Grampa’s truck and drove to Canada for a couple of weeks. My parents spent their time in classes learning about foreign languages. I spent the time doing household chores with my brother and exploring the camp with my new friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then we downsized even further. We had already sent some supplies to be shipped over to Africa in a shipping container. So this time we only took what we could carry on the plane. We packed the suitcases with clothes and supplies we would need for our year in France. All I carried was the red, white, and blue stuffed bear I’d bought at a flea market for a quarter. At eleven years old, I’d whittled down my necessary worldly possessions to one stuffed bear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now, three decades later, I still have that stuffed bear – along with all of the mementoes, clothes, toys, books, and other stuff I’ve acquired since then. I have a house of my own now, and the amount of possessions I own seems to have swelled up to fill every room, shelf, closet, nook, and cranny. I go through periods of downsizing where I sift through piles of clothes and give some to goodwill – I donated ten bags to fundraising clothing drive last summer. But I know I still have much more than I actually need. I just really like knowing that it’s there. At the same time, I think there comes a point where you have so much stuff, you don’t actually know what you have. I own a lot of stuff, and every now and then, I get the vague sensation that some of that stuff may own me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m thinking, it may be time to downsize again – maybe not all the way down to a stuffed bear, but at least enough to be able to close the closet door when company’s coming. This year, I’m going to focus on letting go of my stuff, so that I can hold on more tightly to what’s really important in life.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">I’ve always liked having a lot of stuff around me. I think it started when I was a missionary kid living in Africa where it was harder to get many things. I’d save up my allowance each week, and on those every other year trips to the United States, I’d blow it all on clothes and candy.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Guilt Trip</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/07/guilt-trip/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Guilt Trip" /><published>2018-01-07T11:51:44-05:00</published><updated>2018-01-07T11:51:44-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/07/guilt-trip</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/01/07/guilt-trip/">&lt;p&gt;Chapter 29 of my book In His Hands is called Guilt Trip. In it, I wrote about the guilt I felt when I survived my cancer and others didn’t. “Survivor guilt,” I wrote, “is the feeling that you’ve done something wrong by surviving a traumatic event that others haven’t — an earthquake, a lay-off, a war. It’s also a common side effect of cancer.” I described going to the wake of a dear man who had lost his battle with cancer. “For the moment, I wasn’t afraid of my cancer anymore. I was afraid that a mistake had been made, that the wrong person was in the casket.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Some people survive a cancer diagnosis and go on to do incredible things to make the world better. Others simply survive and go on, which to those around them is an incredible thing that makes the world better. And then, there are those who don’t survive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m probably getting the quote wrong, but sometimes my Christian walk reminds me of the poem about that famous military charge: ‘Theirs not to wonder why. Theirs not to make reply. Theirs but to do and die.’ We just have to keep marching, even when our orders don’t make sense. The comfort? Our orders aren’t based on vanity or false information. Our orders come from the One Who created the world, and Who loved us all enough to let His Son die to bring us safely home.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A dear friend and family member lost a sudden and brief fight with cancer this past November. His immediate family is still learning how to live with the gaping hole in their lives. Another dear friend’s father is currently fighting the battle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever your pains, whatever your struggles, whatever your guilts, I pray that it turns you toward the One Who can bring peace in the storm. In our crazy, spinning world that can turn upside down with a single phone call, please know that you are loved more deeply than you can ever imagine and that this, too, shall pass.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Monica Nelson</name></author><summary type="html">Chapter 29 of my book In His Hands is called Guilt Trip. In it, I wrote about the guilt I felt when I survived my cancer and others didn’t. “Survivor guilt,” I wrote, “is the feeling that you’ve done something wrong by surviving a traumatic event that others haven’t — an earthquake, a lay-off, a war. It’s also a common side effect of cancer.” I described going to the wake of a dear man who had lost his battle with cancer. “For the moment, I wasn’t afraid of my cancer anymore. I was afraid that a mistake had been made, that the wrong person was in the casket.”</summary></entry></feed>